You're marrying a filthy miner-
I warned you.
No one disrespects the
new head of the Morellan family.
Do it again
and I’ll kill you.
You…
Darling, forget it.
We’ll hold the wedding somewhere else.
We can’t fight the Morellan family.
Yes, Livia.
We have to accept it.
We can’t afford to
offend the Morellan family.
What do you mean
we can’t afford it?
I’ve secured Steward Jeyn
of the Sovereign Sanctum?
He’s coming to our wedding today.
Steward Jeyn promised to introduce me
to the Godfather after the ceremony.
The Morellan family is nothing
compared to the Sovereign Sanctum.
That's right!
We have Steward Jeyn
and the entire
Sovereign Sanctum
behind us.
The Morellan family
is nothing in comparison.
Or when Steward,
get on your knees,
entire Morellan  to my family
will pay for your right now.
Exactly!
Kneel and apologize to
my daughter right now,
or we won’t let this go!
We stand with the Scott family!
Make her apologize!
Apologizing to Livia isn’t enough.
She disrespected all of us nobles.
She needs to kneel and
apologize to every single person here.
Apologize!
I’d like to see who dares.